rwgusa.com 2015-11-13

# Privacy Policy for Domain Registration and Internet Marketing

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and share information and data when you use this website (“Site”). By visiting or using all or any part of this Site, you consent to this Privacy Policy.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you (“Personal Information”) when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We collect personal information only if you choose to share it with us. The decision to provide this information is optional, however, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to utilize certain features of the Site.

We automatically collect anonymous usage information from you when you visit the Site (“Usage Data”). Usage Data is anonymous usage information such as the type of web browser you use, your operating system, your internet service provider, your IP address, the pages that you view on the Site, and the time and duration of your visits to the Site. We use this information to help us improve and enhance the services on the Site.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  1. To personalize and improve your experience. Your Personal Information and Usage Data helps us to better respond to your individual needs including processing of transactions, notification of new products or services, customization of services, and to communicate with you.
  2. To offer 3rd party services. Certain services on the Site may be provided by 3rd parties (“Service Providers”). We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary or helpful for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each service provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than for the purpose for which such information was provided or authorized by you.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your Personal Information. We employ reasonable physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no data transmitted over the internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. While we strive to protect information transmitted on our through the Site, we do not guarantee the security of any information you upload, store, share, transmit or provide on your through the Site.

**Do we use cookies?**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the Site to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We may use cookies in connection with your usage of the Site. We do not use cookies to collect personal information. You may set your browser to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies, though either of these actions may affect your use of the Site.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Information. This does not include trusted 3rd Party Service Providers who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about our Site.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from visitors under the age of 13. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13, we will terminate any account that user may have with us and will delete any Personal Information that they have submitted from our records.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.rwgusa.com/contact_us.htm).
